Does it look good?
To become a woman who makes people intoxicated
and lose control.
The first step
is to casually attract the prey's attention.
Tell her to come to my office.
Mr. Ling, you wanted to see me?
You did well in court.
These are rewards for you.
Pick one.
Mr. Ling, these are too valuable.
I can't accept them.
What's wrong?
Don't you like it?
No.
I'm really happy to have your approval.
But these gifts are too valuable.
I can't accept them.
If you really want to reward me,
then please give me more work.
Really?
This is the first time I've heard of such a reward.
I still have a lot to learn.
Once I've learned enough,
I'll definitely ask you for a big gift.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
If there's nothing else, I'll head back first.
Why didn't you take the reward?
That wasn't a reward.
It was clearly a way to buy me off.
Of course I couldn't take it.
Besides.
This is the second step the book taught me.
First, you have to catch the prey's attention.
Then,
weaken his advantage.
I really don't understand your generation.
You make everything so complicated.
Because you're just an old fossil who doesn't understand anything.
Wh-What do you mean by an antique?
Sister Cheng, this is the live stream schedule.
Please take a look.
What does this mean?
It's changed to a group stream?
Sister, this is the company's new live stream adjustment.
From today on,
you will appear as a group.
As the captain,
you will lead our newcomers to stream together.
What do you mean?
Why didn't anyone notify me in advance?
I'm not sure about this either.
Li Qianqian,
why did no one tell me about the change in the live stream format?
You are already washed up.
To ease the public pressure from the previous lawsuit,
we need to cultivate other influencers.
If you want to leech off my traffic, just say so.
Why are you doing a group stream?
Let me tell you,
I don't accept this.
Mucheng,
face reality.
This is your only option right now.
Look at the others.
Cut the crap.
Do you not understand what I'm saying?
I don't accept this.
Mucheng,
don't forget you are just a pawn.
You can only follow orders.
Face reality and don't back out.
If you don't accept it, legal will handle it as a breach of contract.
You...
Who do you think you are,
talking to me like that?
And who do you think you are?
Okay, we can start now.
Alright.
Hello, brothers.
I'm Mucheng.
Did you miss me?
Don't believe those rumors online.
I didn't have a falling out with the company.
And from now on,
I will use a brand new streaming format
to meet you all.
Say something...
Welcome the new streamer.
Say something.
Say hello.
We will keep you company together.
[VIP Internal Group (Members: 8)]
Thank you, Mr. Wang, for the gift.
Thank you.
Thank you, Brother Cui.
Thank you, Unknown Artist.
Thank you, Earthly Beauty and Enthusiastic Audience.
Thank you for your company.
Thank you.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Baby Mucheng, you are the main character.
We are here to see you.
Say something...
She must have been forced by the company, right?
Now they're bringing in newbies to siphon her traffic.
Congratulations to Mucheng for winning the premiere PK.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Tell them we're having a celebration party tonight.
Yes, Boss Ling.
Look, look!
They took the bait.
I told you it would work.
Put it away.
Almost done.
Help me. Help.
Help me.
Let me go. Let me go.
Memories sealed for nearly a thousand years
Help me.
were released just because of a smile.
Recalling that person again,
my heart is still filled with regret.
That wound that can never heal
is torn open again.
Put it away.
Almost done.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
Step three of the strategy:
Constantly renew your freshness
in the prey's mind.
Cheers!
Then I'll call him over for a drink.
Shameless.
How can a woman be so easy?
To achieve her goal,
she doesn't even care about her dignity.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'll drink up. Drink as you please.